YASHVARDHAN JADHAV

Indore, Madhya Pradesh

■ 8109212860 | 🗷 yashvardhann743@gmail.com | 🔏 yashvardhan-jadhav.netlify.app | 🖸 github.com/yashvardhanJadhav | 🛅

linkedin.com/in/yashvardhan-jadhav-319621200

Personal Profile

I am a student of Medi-caps University, Indore with a major in Computer Science. My goal is to get a job in the Information Technology field after graduating. I enjoy solving technical problems, researching and developing new technologies, designing software applications.

Education

Medi-Caps University

Indore, India

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science August 2020 - present

Score - 9.29 CGPA

Saraswati Vidya Mandir Mandsaur, India

Higher Secondary August 2019 - March 2020

Score - **91.8 Percentage**

Saraswati Vidya Mandir

Mandsaur, India

Secondary August 2017 - March 2018

Score - 83.8 Percentage

Experience

Medi-Caps University

Indore, India

IEEE Conference Website Sept 2022 - current

• Created a website on IEEE International Conference held in Medi-caps University with guidance of Teacher.

- Created a website of filed international conference need in wedi-caps of inversity with guidance of read
- **Technical Skills:** HTML, CSS, Javascript, React JS, Tailwind CSS.
- Designed approved by IEEE.
- **Soft Skills:** Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills.

Medi-Caps University Indore, India

International Conference on Business Perspectives Website

Jan 2023 - present

- Created a website on International Conference on Business Perspectives in Medi-caps University with guidance of Teacher.
- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React JS, Tailwind CSS.
- **Soft Skills:** Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills.

Projects

Resume Builder Dec 2022 - Jan 2023

Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Mongoose, React JS, Express JS, Node JS, Tailwind CSS

- Resume Builder is Web Application for creating Professional Resumes.
- Resume Builder has user Login / SignUp Functionality for User and provide different templates for resumes.

CryptoTracker Dec 2021 - Jan 2022

Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React JS, Tailwind CSS

- CryptoTracker is a web application which displays crypto currency detailed analysis.
- CryptoTracker takes the data from API and shows the live detailed analysis of all crypto coins.

NoteSaver May 2022 - June 2022

Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Mongoose, React JS, Express JS, Node JS, Tailwind CSS

- Note Saver is a web application which stores your notes and have user Login / SignUp Functionality for User.
- Note Saver give option to edit, delete the note and It has stong user Authentication System

Skills_

Programming HTML, CSS, Javascript, C/C++, Data Structure and Algorithm, Mongoose, Express, React, Node, Tailwind CSS

Miscellaneous Linux, Microsoft Office, Github.

Soft Skills Adaptability, Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Patience

Others

Coding 150+ Questions solved on Leetcode and 250+ Questions solved on codechef and 100 Question on Geeks for Geeks

JULY 25, 2023